Kibildis, Melba CIRL Annual Meeting Materials 6359
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Melba Kibildis CIRL Annual Meeting Materials
1978-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Cataflio, Maria
Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians (CIRL)
Kibildis, Melba
6359
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
8234261
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 20, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5171: Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians (CIRL) Records 5171 P: Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians (CIRL) 38th Annual Conference Photographs 6359 P: Maria Cataflio CIRL Photographs
Cataflio, Maria; Kibildis, Melba; Committee of Industrial Relations Librarians
8234261
- 32nd Annual Meeting, MIT, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 33rd Annual Meeting, Toronto, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 34th Annual Meeting, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 35th Annual Meeting, Cornell University, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 36th Annual Meeting, Ann Arbor, MI, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 37th Annual Meeting, Minneapolis, MN, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 38th Annual Meeting, Princeton, NJ, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 39th Annual Meeting, Edmonton, Alberta, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 40th Annual Meeting, Wayne State University, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 41st Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  Joint Meeting with the Industrial Relations Research Association (IRRA)
- 41nd Annual Meeting, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 55th Annual Meeting, Princeton, NJ, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 55th Annual Meeting, Detroit, MI, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Melba Kibildis CIRL History and Mementos, 1982-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)